我们终于到了
We made itl
说 蜜月第一天
Say"honeymoon day one. "
蜜月第一天
Honeymoon day onel
你在拍照吗
Are you taking a picture?
视频
Video
我想看你还能撑多久
I wanted to see how long until you broke.
你好 我是拉斐尔
Hi. I'm Rafael
-你好  -这是我女儿 伊丽丝
Hello! That's my daughter, Elise.
伊丽丝 你好 我是约翰 她是贝莉
Elise, hi, I'm John. That's Bailey.
-你好  -你好
Hellol Hi
海滨之妙是我们开的
And we run the Oceanside Dreams.
你们预订了一间豪华别墅
I know that you booked our Iuxury villa.
-没错  -对
YeahYes.
送你们过去吧
So let's get you in there, yeah?
我喜欢豪华
Oh, I like the sound of luxury.
你之前说的是别墅吧
You did say, villa, right?
对 没错
Yes. Yes, sir.
最近经历了几次飓风 还没完全恢复如初
We're still recovering from the last few hurricanes.
有时会停电
The power goes out sometimes.
网有时候是好的
The intemet works sometimes.
但对我们来说 仍然是天堂
But to us, this is still paradise.
完全同意
Totally.
只是网上的照片
It's just that the pictures on the website,
有点不一样
they look a little different.
你说得没错
Yes, exactly.
我们用A|生成渲染图
We used AI to generate renderings.
按照入的理解 照片是这个地方
So those are photos of what the place feels like,
给人的感觉
yeah, according to the AI
这也是我们跟其它度假村的不同之处
That's what separates us from the other resorts.
虚假广告吗
The false advertising?
那是什么声音
What was that?
很可能是负鼠
possums, most likely.
它们声音很大
They are loud.
但请放心 不管听见啥声
But rest assured, if you hear anything atall,
要么是交配的声音 要么是猎杀的声音
it's either a mating sound or a killing soynd.
祝你们蜜月快乐
Happy honeymoon.
好吧
OK.
不错
That's good.
不 肯定会很棒的
No, this is gonna be great.
这里
This is
太对不起了
I am so sorry.
♪我会为你披荆斩棘♪
♪Imgonna win for you♪
♪一切如你所愿♪
♪Like I know youiwant me to do♪
♪Like Iknow you want re to do ♪
你睡觉了吗
Hey, did you get any sleep?
只要考过了我就睡
I will sleep when I pass this exam.
好吧
Yeah.
你要是当上警探
I don't think you're gonna sleep more
更睡不了
after you make detective.
怎么样了
How's it going?
专业知识部分应该没问题
I feel pretty good about my knowledge.
笔试很简单
I mean, the written portion was easy.
但让我整宿睡不着的
But the oral exam is what is literally
就是口试
keeping me up at night.
这个测试太主观了
I mean, the test is so subjective.
只要有一个考官反对
If even one person on the panel has it against me,
我就完了
I mean, it's over.
你觉得普利姆警督还是讨厌你吗
And you think Lieutenant Primm still hates you?
我送他自己做的饼干
I brought him homemade cookies,
他却丢垃圾桶了
and he threw them in the trash.
好吧 你控制不了普利姆
OK. You can't control Primm.
只能控制自己
You can only control you.
而你现在应该
And now it's time for you
远离荧光笔
to step away from the highlighter.
等下 不 不 不行
Wait. No, no, no, no, no.
说得非常正确 你想
That's exactly right, though. See?
正因为我只能控制自己 所以我需要做到完美
Because I can only control me, so I just need to be perfect.
你会复习过头的
You can over- prepare.
不 这是懒人给自己找的借口
No, that is an idea that lazy people created.
不 我见过这种事 真的
No, I've seen it happen, OK?
你太执着了
You get in your own head.
你只要相信自己 然后放手
You just need to trust yourself and then let it go.
算了吧 我觉得我做不到
Yeah, I don't think I can do that.
好吧
AlI right.
我去洗个澡
I'm gonna take a shower.
现在吗
Right now?
对
Yeah.
那
Well- -
也许我可以休息一下
Hmm, maybe I could take a break.
当时是在婚礼上
It was a wedding, you know.
那些音乐 灯光都很浪漫
Everything was all romantic- music, soft light- -
我好像
and I kind of
亲了塞琳娜
kissed Celina.
你的同事塞琳娜吗
Celina, who you work with?
你中枪时救了你一命的
Celina, who saved your life when you were shot?
-那个塞琳娜吗  -对
That Celina? - Yeah.
我提到灯光了吗
Did I mention the light?
因为找真的觉得那个光照气氛
Because I really believe, like, the mood lighting
要负20%的责任
was 20%responsible.
她什么反应
How did she react?
不怎么好
Not good.
她给的表情是介于恐惧
Yeah, the look she gave me was somewhere between horrified
和非常恐惧之间
and really horrified.
她不懂你的感受吗
She doesn't share your feelings?
连我自己都不确定我的感受
I'm not sure I share my feelings, you know.
我们一直关系很好 她是唯一一个
We've been so close, and she was the only person
-我可以倾述的人  -听着
I could talk to. - Look.
把这种关系和情爱之类的感觉混淆
It's very natural to confuse that kind of bond
是很正常的事
with something romantic.
好吧 那我该怎么做
OK. So- - so what do I do?
该怎么弥补
How do I fix this?
你跟塞琳娜一起经历了很多
You and Celina have been through a lot together.
你们共同经历了创伤
You have a shared trauma.
不管你有多想
And as tempting as it is
在一夜之间解决所有问题
to want everything fixed overnight,
但这都不是办法
that's not how these things work.
你说的创伤 指的是
Now, when you say trauma, are you talking
塞丽娜拒绝我 还是我中枪的事
about Celina rejecting me or me getting shot?
因为在我看来两者伤我一样重
Because they have been equally traumatizing in my eyes.
你们是成年人了
You're both adults
消除误会
Clear the air.
设定一些健康的界限 给她点时间
Set some healthy boundaries and give her time.
好吧
OK.
我们要创建唯粉网账号吗
Are we starting an OnlyFans?
onlyFans是一个互联网内容订阅服务 该平台有大量成人模特使用
我以为咱们要把这次蜜月之旅
I thought we would want to remember
永远记录下来
this honeymoon forever.
但现在我不太确定要不要
Now of course, I'm not so sure.
这是纽扣摄像头吗
Is this a button cam?
还有无人机
A drone? Mm- hmm.
咱们是要开情报局吗
Are we launching an intelligence agency?
这是一套的 而且还打折
It came as a package, and it was on sale.
我就激情下单了
And I got excited.
给你看看吧
Can I show you?
这个是防水的
This one is waterproof.
非常适合游泳划皮艇的时候用
It makes it perfect for swimming, kayaking.
或者我们可以跟鲨鱼一起笼中潜水
Or we can do that thing where we go cage diving with sharks.
不行 这里没有这个项目
We can't. They don't have it here.
我确认过了
Oh. I made sure.
这个我们穿戴在身上
This one attaches right to us.
等我们高空滑索时 你在上面滑
So when we go zip lining and you're zipping on past
我在地上看
and I'm watching from the ground,
我们后期可以剪成不同的角度
we can cut into it later from all sorts of different angles.
还有这个是纽扣摄像头
OK, and this one is a button camera in case
以防万一我们要搞卧底
we have to go undercover,
捣毁什么贩毒团伙
break up any monkey drug cartels,
那这个呢
And what about this one?
怎么这么黑
Oh, why is it so dark?
等下
Hang on a second.
-夜视镜  -不行
Night visionNo.
-可以  -不行
Yes. - No.
完全可以 听着
Totally. Just listen.
听我说
Listen.
我是想咱们可以把这些安装起来
I was thinking we can take one of these, set it up,
就是装外面
you know, outside.
看那些负鼠在干什么
See what the possums are doing.
对 你原来是这么想的
Oh, yeah, totally, that's what you were thinking.
我就是这么想的
It is what I was thinking.
你想的啥
What were you thinking?
我觉得你知道我想的啥
I think you know what I was thinking.
我都结婚了
Hey, I'm married.
塞琳娜 你好啊
Celina, hil
艾伦
Aaron.
你可以回来巡逻了吗
Are you cleared for active duty?
不 还没
No, uh, not yet.
快了
Soon.
我有东西要给你
I, um I got something for you.
来的路上买的
Picked it up on the way to work.
不 你不用这样做的
Oh. No, you didn't have to do that.
惊喜吧 新笔记本
Surprise. New laptop.
艾伦 真的完全没必要
Aaron, that's completely unnecessary.
但你说你的电脑有点慢
Yeah, but you were saying how your computer was slow.
我知道你在干什么
I know what you're doing
你是想道歉
You're trying to apologize for the- -
因为那个吻 但其实没必要
for the kiss, but you don't have to.
好吗
OK?
好
OK.
好吧
Yeah.
有人想要笔记本电脑吗
Anybody want a laptop?
有 我要
Yeah. Yeah, I'll take itl
命案现场例外是一种认识误区
The murder scene exception is the misbelief
它认为在极端可怕的命案现场
that when a crime scene is so heinous,
执法人员可以不取得搜查令进入该区域
you are allowed to go around the search warrant.
又对了 下一题
Correct again. Next question.
我最喜欢的休闲活动是什么
What is my favorite leisure activity?
什么
Um, excuse me?
就是我更喜欢户外还是室内
You know am I more of an outdoor or indoor cat?
斯密提 求你照着我给你的卡上面念 行吗
Smitty, please just read from the cards I gave you, OK?
是你征求我的建议
Look, you asked me for my advice.
我没有
I did not!
我的建议是
And my advice is,
你应该调查一下普利姆
you should do a little research on Primm.
弄清他喜欢什么 不喜欢什么 有什么爱好
Find out his likes, his dislikes, favorite hobbies.
然后就能靠这些信息
Then you can take that knowledge
赚些额外分
and score some bonus points.
我担心在上次袭击事件后
I'm worried that I focused too much on Aaron
我过于关注艾伦 没有帮到你
after the attack and did you a disservice,
忽略了你的感受
let you fall through the cracks.
谢谢 长官
Oh, thank you, sir,
我没事
but I'm fine.
那次婚礼呢
What about the wedding?
你无视纪律
You went rogue.
你应该知道没有请示其它警官的情况下
You know better than to meet with a CI
不能和线人见面的
without alerting other officers.
我知道 我只是觉得
do. I just thought that- -
这样会给我留下好印象
It would impress me?
并没有
Well, it didn't
差一点就酿成大祸
That situation could have ended a lot worse.
-不要再这样了 - 是 长官
Don't ever do it again. - Yes, ma'am.
哈珀需要重回警探团队
Harper is needed back with the detectives.
你会和布拉福德警司搭档直到诺兰回来
you'll be riding with Sergeant Bradford until Nolan returns.
-是 长官  -走吧
Yes, sir Let's gO ADFORD
拿上作战包 菜鸟 把警车准备好
Get the war bags, Boot. Set up the shop.
他喜欢狗
He's a major dog guy.
每个周韦他都去动物庇护所
He goes to the shelter every weekend
去找些新狗子来收养
looking for new ones to foster.
除非给他们找到永久的家
And he won't stop until he sets them up
否则他是不会罢手的
with their forever homes.
等等 这可真不错
i Wait, what that is beautiful.
我也喜欢狗子啊
I am also a dog lover.
i 你们干嘛呢
What's going on here?
我在帮陈准备警探考试呢
I'm helping Chen study for her detective's exam.
斯密提
Smitty.
说好的不要复习过头呢
What happened to not over- preparing?
是斯密提非要这样 但估计你也不信
It's Smitty. Is it even really helping?
什么
What?
再几分钟就好
I just need a few minutes.
不行 你需要喘口气
No, you need to take a break.
赛琳娜今天跟我
I got Celina today
走吧 你跟我们一车
Come on. You're riding with us.
听上去挺有意思的嘛
Well, that actually sounds kind of fun.
要是你们俩敢再聊星盘
The second you two start talking about birth charts,
我就把你们俩都踢下车
I'm kicking you both out of the car.
好吧 谢了 斯密提谢谢
OK. Thank you, Smitty, thank you.
我能做的都做了
I've done all I can do.
剩下的就靠她自己了
The rest is up to her.
行吧
Right.
伊丽丝算是说对了
Elise was right.
这地方也太美了吧
This place is beautiful!
我们只要有彼此就够了 对吧
And all we really need is each other, you know?
难以置信
Oh! Unbelievable.
怎么了
What?
我只是在看负鼠相机
Oh, I'm just checking the possum camera, man.
它们还真挺投入的
They were really going at it.
打架吗还是
Fighting or you know?
还以为只有咱俩待在
I thought we were the only ones staying
岛的这一头呢
on this end of the island.
也许他在我们之后到的
Uh, maybe he got here after us?
看上去他是在自省
He looks introspective.
他看着像是个吸血鬼
He looks like a vampire
正在竭尽全力避免照到太阳
trying to avoid sunlight at all costs.
这我可真没想到
I wasn't expecting that.
不是说你带上了所有相机
Just because you brought all the cameras
就得每时每刻都用上
doesn't mean you can use them all the time.
你说的太对了
You're totally right.
享受当下
Be in the moment.
不是 我听进去你说的话了
No, it's- Ican hear what you're saying.
稍等一下
Wait a second.
有新瓜
Update.
他不是吸血鬼
He is not a vampire.
他在吃 鳄犁吐司吗
He is eating avocado toast?
你觉得他会是什么人呢
So who do you think he is?
我觉得应该是个亿万富翁公子哥儿
Uh, I'm gonna go with billionaire playboy
伪造了自己的死亡 去做了整容手术
faking his own death, went under the knife
好跟自己的第二个家室
to change his features to start a new life
重新开始新生活
with a secret second family
亿万富翁 但是他住这儿哎
Billionaire? But he chose to stay here.
也是 也许他迷路了吧
Oh. Yeah maybe he's lost.
Oh, Yeah, maybe he's lost.
-我去跟他聊聊  -不不不 等等
fm gonna go talk to him. No, no, no, wait
I'm gonna go talk to himNo, no, no, wait
如果他只想自己一个人待着呢
What if he just wants to be Ieft alone?
或者更糟糕 如果他不想一个人
Or even worse, he doesn't want to be left alone,
那我们蜜月的后半截就必须带着个电灯泡了
and then we have a thirdl wheel for the rest of our honeymoon.
我只是想了解下他的情况
Ijust want to get a read on him.
而且你别担心 我会让他觉得
And don't worry, I'll make it sound
咱们俩都是老人家 很无趣
like we're old and no fun.
等我跟他聊完 他肯定想躲我们远远的
By the time Im dlone, he won't want to be anywhere near us.
好吧
OK.
你也可以不用把我们说的太无趣
You can make us sound a little fun.
嗨 我是约翰·诺兰
Hi, I'm John Nolan.
坐在那边的是我光彩照人的老婆 贝莉
That over there is my stunning wife, Bailey. "
矮油 还真是 她可真美
Wow, yes, she is really beautiful. "
那还用说
"Yeah, she is.
不止呢 她还有才华 聪明
"Did I also mention she's talented and smart
幽默 而且
and funny and- "
这也太赞了吧
"That's so amazing.
你可真幸运 兄弟
You're so lucky, dude. "
我确保步话机电池充好电了
I made sure my radio batteries are charged up.
我还多拿了个富余的 以防方一嘛
And I have a spare one here too because you never know.
我在后备箱多放了一箱水所以
I threw an extra case of water in the back, so- -
华雷斯
Juarez.
我这就闭嘴
I'll stop.
嘿 你和亚伦怎么样了
Hey, what's going on with you and Aaron?
没事啊 怎么了
Nothing. Why?
我看你们俩在停车场
Well, I saw you guys in the parking lot,
有点小尴尬的样
and it looked awkward.
我不知道
Huh, I don't know.
好吧 是有一点 我就是
OK, just a little. I just - whoa, whoa, whoa.
-你们俩都给我下车  -不是吧
Both of you, out now. - Whoa.
你说不能聊星盘
You said no birth charts.
你没说我们不能聊其他男生啊
You didn't say we couldn't talk about boys.
这还用说吗
That goes without saying.
那我们午餐时再聊好了
We will talk at lunch.
7M100 在贝尔维尤和东肯辛顿大街交汇处
Seven- Metro- one hundred, I have a four- eighty- four
正在发生一起盗窃案
in progress at Bellevue&East Kensington.
我们这就过去
Show us responding
我可以的
I've got this.
先生
Sir!
请你马上站住
I need you to stop right there.
是里面出事了吗
Oh, is- - is something going on with- -
我们收到报警说有人
Oh, we got a report of someone shoplifting
正在这个位置入店行窃
at this location.
不是我
Wasn't me.
你能把胳膊举起来给我看看吗
Well, can you raise your arms for me?
抱歉
I'm sorry.
我就是 我胳膊好疼
I just- - my arm really hurt,
而且我没有钱
and I don't have any money.
好吧 我们需要送你去医院
OK, we need to get you to the hospital.
你叫什么
What s your name?
我不知道
I don't know.
上面说你叫乔纳森·奈特
Well, it says here your name is Jonathan Knight,
你在信任安保公司工作
and you work for Trusted Security.
我叫这名字吗
Is that my name?
乔纳森·奈特
Jonathan Knight.
行了 别演了
OK, drop the act.
假装不知道自己名字
Lying about your name isn't gonna
我们也要逮捕你
keep us from arresting you.
-手铐  -不不不
Cuff him. - No! No, no, no, no.
我 我醒过来就发现自己在流血
I- - I woke up, and I was just bleeding!
然后我看到了便利店
And I saw the convenience store.
我 之前的事我一点都不记得了
I- - Idon't remember anything from before that.
行了 走吧
AlI righty, let's go.
那是石膏粉吗
Is that plaster dust?
我 我不知道啊
I- - I don't know.
你信他说的吗
Are you buying any of this?
一个字都不信
Not a word.
他胳膊上的口子不像是装的
I mean, the gash in his arm is real enough.
我觉得不太舒服
I don't feel that good.
不 没事 没事
No, it's OK It's OK
我们 我们送你去医院吧
We're gonna- - we're gonna take you to the hospital.
不不
No, no.
给呕吐男叫救护车吧
Pukester is going in an ambulance,
你跟他一起去
and you're going with him.
我们能聊聊早餐的那个人吗
Can we talk about that guy from breakfast?
这也太奇怪了
I mean, that was weird.
我问他叫啥 他花了5秒钟
When I asked him his name, it took him a full five seconds
才说自己叫迪安
to tell me it was Dean.
可能是他止痛药劲儿还没过吧
It's probably cause he's on pain meds
其实整容手术挺难搞的
Any kind of facial surgery is quite serious.
说不好
I don't know.
给我讲了个狗咬他的奇怪故事
Told me a wonky story about a dog attack.
感觉不太对头
Something about it just doesn't smell right.
你现在能别用警察头脑思考问题吗
Can you tum you cop brain off for just a few hours
我们还要去划独木舟呢
so we can go kayaking?
当然可以
Of course I can.
我把这个小美人先着陆
Let me just land this little beauty.
-憋紧张  -小心了
Don't be alarmed. - Careful.
只需要一个按钮就能落地
Lands with the touch of a button.
嘿
Hey - ooh.
抱歉
And I'm sorry.
你能再说一遍吗 我好做个记录
Could you just state it one more time for the record?
-你赢了  -嗯嗯
You beat me. - Uh- huh.
所以嘞
Which means?
就是我输了呗
Which means that I lost.
你的进步可真是惊人
You really had a staggering improvement.
如果你想换个职业
If you ever wanted a second career change,
你可以去做职业独木舟选手
you could be a professional kayaker.
那你吸取到什么教训了呢
And what is the lesson here?
就是别没事跟人比赛
That don't make everything
除非确保我能赢
a contest unless I'm sure I can win.
没错啦
That's right.
是我们没关吗
Did we leave that open?
也许之前就这样
Maybe it was like that before?
行吧
Yeah.
也许我们是被这里的壮丽景色
We were just too distracted
分散了注意力所以没发现
by the grandeur of this place to notice?
几点了
What time is it?
8点半
It's 8: 30.
完美
Oh, perfect!
好
OK.
还能躺会儿
Just a second to lie down.
然后咱去吃晚饭
Then we'll grab some dinner.
我跟贝莉一早上都心惊胆战
Bailey and I had somewhat of a stressful morning.
昨晚摄像头没关
The camera I left on last night recorded
拍到有人在门外看我们睡觉
someone standing outside our window watching us sleep.
-看了一个小时呢 - 对
For almost an hour. Right.
所以我给所有摄像头都充了电
So I have charged all the cameras.
我们要搭建一个先进的
We are setting up a small but very
小范围警备区
technologically advanced perimeter.
看他还会不会再回来
Let's see if he wants to come back.
再让你看我睡觉
Watch me sleep now.
♪都整上大金牙 我喜欢这样的女孩♪
♪All gold teeth, Llike my girls like that♪
♪从不微笑♪
♪And never smiling♪
♪我喜欢女孩这么打扮♪
♪I like my girls like that♪
♪让混蛋拜倒♪
♪Dirty- ass knees♪
♪我喜欢那样的女孩♪
♪I like my girls like that, Llike my girls like that♪
启动开了
It's on.
我们这是疯了吗
Are we being crazy?
昨晚有人偷窥我们睡觉整整一个小时
Somebody watched us sleep last night for an hour.
这才叫疯了
That's crazy.
我们为什么就不能过个正常的蜜月呢
Why can't we have, like, a normal honeymoon?
这样吧 我们坐第一班轮渡离开这里
Tejl you what, let's take the first ferry out of here.
等我们回到家 马上重订行程
When we get home, we're gonna book a trip
去天底下最正常的地方
to the most normal place we can find.
是伊丽丝
It's Elise.
来了
Coming!
♪我就喜欢这样的姑娘♪
♪I like my girls like that♪
-你好啊  -客房服务来咯
Hey, thereHousekeeping.
进来吧
Come on in.
给你拿了两条干净毛巾
Brought you two some fresh towels.
谢谢你
Thank you.
伊丽丝 下一班离开的渡轮是什么时候
Um, Elise, when is the next ferry out of here?
今夭肯定没了 明天可能也没有
No ferry today or tomorrow probably.
靠谱程度快赶上这里的网络和电力了
It's about as reliable as the internet and the power.
但我相信到你们退房的时候 渡轮肯定
But Im sure it'll be up and running by the time
整装待发 静候二位了
you guys check oyt
如果出问题了怎么办
What if there was a problem?
有什么问题吗
Is there a problem?
没有 没有 就这样吧
No, no. That's it
谢谢你
Thank you.
好的还需要什么随时告诉我
OK, let me know if you need anything else.
-好吧  -那行
AlI right. OK.
♪我喜欢这样的姑娘♪
♪I like my girls like that♪
♪I like my girls like that ♪
♪我喜欢这样的姑娘♪
好吧 我们还得在这儿多呆几天
Well, we are stuck here for a few more days.
那就充分利用这段时间吧
So we might as well make the most of it.
-我们去游泳好吗  -当然 没问题
Shall we go for a swim? - Sure, of course.
没错 充分利用时间
Yeah, letls make the best of this.
来吧
Come on.
♪我喜欢这样的姑娘♪
♪I like my girls like that♪
嘿 卢娜 新工作感觉怎么样
Hey, Luna. How's the new job going?
挺能激励我的
Energizing, mostly.
当一个患者顾问让我觉得很有意义
Being a patient advocate is rewarding.
实际上 我们是来调查一个病人的
Um, we're actually here to check up on a patient
就是我们昨天送来的那个
that we brought in yesterday.
他声称自己有失忆症
He claimed to have amnesia.
没错
Right.
415房的那个无名氏
The John Doe in 415.
我给其他的医院流浪汉收容所 戒毒所打过电话
I have called other hospitals, homeless shelters,
能想到的地方我都打过电话了
rehab facilities- anything I can think of.
都没有他失踪的报案记录
No one has reported him missing.
医生认为他能恢复记忆吗
Do the doctors think he'll get his memory back?
可能吧
Probably.
脑损伤可能很棘手
But brain injuries can be tricky,
所以可能要等几个月
so it could be a few months.
好吧 谢谢
OK. Thanks.
我们去和他谈谈
We'll go talk to him.
嘿 艾伦怎么样了
Hey, how's Aaron?
我觉得他挺好吧
He's fine, I think.
我也说不好
I- - I don't know.
我感觉没这么简单
I sense trouble.
不不 并不是
No, no not at all.
好吧 确实有点麻烦
OK, maybe a little.
他在婚礼上莫名其妙吻了我
He kissed me at the wedding out of nowhere.
现在我
And now I'm
生气吗
Angry?
是的
Yeah.
我觉得他只是糊涂了
I think he was just confused.
我觉得自己的反应
And I mean, the way Ireacted,
一定让场面相当尴尬吧
it must have been so embarrassing.
我敢肯定他恨不能忘掉一切
And Im sure he wants to forget it ever happened.
你说的这些艾伦的感受 都是你自以为的
I'm hearing a lot about what you think Aaron's feeling.
但只有你勇敢说出口 你才能知道答案
But you can't know until you talk it through.
你们找到什么线索了吗
Did you find something?
你们知道我是谁吗
You know who I am?
恐怕还没有
I'm afraid not.
听着 我们联系了可信保安公司
Look, we contacted Trusted Security.
但他们从没听说过你
They have never heard of you.
而且在加州我们也找不到
And we can't find a Jonathan Knight
符合你描述的这个乔纳森·奈特
matching your description in California.
我一直在思考这件事
Well, I have been thinking about it.
而我认为唯一合理的答案是
And I think the only rational answer is that.
我是个间谍
Im, a spy
-我觉得不能够  -不
Not my first guess. No.
不 其实挺合理的 这是一个掩护身份
No, it makes sense. It's a cover identity.
我可能是要渗透进
I was probably infiltrating a high- rise
满是绝密资料的政府大楼
full of government secrets.
也许我中毒了
Maybe I got poisoned.
所以我才会吐的
That's why I threw up.
你懂的 就像辐射中毒之类的
You know, like radiation poisoning or something?
好吧 我们先不要妄下结论
Yeah, you know, let's not jump to conclusions.
你会呕吐可能是因为你脑震荡了
You probably threw up because you're concussed.
朝鲜 南朝鲜
KorearNorth Korea
等等 我现在都想起来了 z
Wait, it's all coming back to me now.
我的目标是朝鲜
I- - I was targeting North Korea.
我的曰标是朝鲜
I- Iwas targeting North Korea
我有一个搭档 我们在执行一项任务
And I had a partnerfand we were on a missidg.
你知道他在哪儿吗
Do you know where re is?
他可能有危险
He could be in danger.
我们得找到他
We need to find him
你知道你搭档的名字吗
Um, do you know your partner's name
你最后一次见到他是什么时候
or when you last saw him?
不记得了
No.
好吧 我们再去查
OK, we're on it.
回头再来找你
We'll get back to you.
你怎么把电视关了
You tumed off the TV?
有没有可能他是对的
Any chance he's right?
我们查了他的指纹
We ran his prints.
如果他真在那个传说中的机构工作
If he worked for a three- letter agency,
那系统早就报警了
it would have set off alarms.
是啊 我是也许吧
Yeah. I mean, maybe.
但他谈到搭档的方式 让人感觉很真实
But the way he talked about his partner, that felt real.
也许他的话里隐藏了一些事实
Maybe there's some kernel of truth there.
你也看到新闻了
You saw the news.
他只是在重复在电视上看到的东西
He's just repeating the last thing he saw on TV.
也许他触发了某些回忆
Maybe there's some memory that's surfacing,
可他就是搞不懂是什么意思
and he just can't make sense of what it really means.
也许吧
Maybe.
不管怎样 我们现在也无能为力
Regardless, there's not much we can do
除非他再想起些什么
until he starts to remember more.
打扰
Excuse me.
你看到布拉福德警官和陈警官了吗
Have you seen Officers Bradford and Chen?
那我麻烦大了
Then Im in trouble.
看看吧
Look at this.
她在那里
There she is.
太漂亮了
So nice.
贝莉
Baileyl
普通的蜜月
Normal honeymoonl
我想要的不过是一个普通的蜜月
Just wanted a normal honeymoon.
好的
OK.
好的 我是洛杉矶警局的约翰·诺兰
OK. This is John Nolan, LAPD.
和我一起的是紧急医疗技术员贝莉·努恩
With me is Bailey Nune, EMT.
我们刚刚发现了一具尸体
We have just discovered a dead body
女性 30多岁 玛莎什么来的
Uh, female, 30s, Martha
德尔加朵
Oh, Delgado
她的身体已经僵硬了
Her body is still stiff.
她已经死了至少日个小时了
She's been dead for at least eight hours.
浸在水里的时间不太长 尸体还没受到太大破坏
Wasn'tjn the waterlong enough to sustain much damage.
真是个悲剧
It's such a tragedy.
我得说 这种情况并不像你想的那么罕见
I gotta say, it's not as uncommon as you might think.
什么意思
What do you mean?
哪怕是这里土生土长的人
Well, even people who grew up here,
有时候也会低估暗流的力量
they sometimes underestimate the undertow.
有些人喝了几杯小酒 想在晚上来个夜泳
They have a few drinks, they go for a night swim,
然后 然后就这样了
and then- - then this happens.
也许是吧
Well, that may be.
但相信你不反对
But I'm sure you'll agree,
我们得找一些专业人士
we do need to call some professionals
来确定到底发生了什么导致死亡
to determine what really happened.
那是当然
Oh, of course
Oh, of course.
我已经打电话给主岛的警察了
I already called the constables on the main island.
他们说会尽快赶到这里
And they said they're gonna get here as soon as they can.
有时候隔个几天
It's usually just a couple of days
就会发生意外溺水
with the accidental drowning.
但我们得把可怜的玛莎放进
But we'll put poor Martha here
步入式冰箱里 直到主岛警察赶到
in the walk- in fridge until they arrive.
好的 哦 我手机有信号了
Right. Ohl I've got bars.
只有一格信号 我介意我用一下吗
I've got a bar. I'm gonna- - would you?
拿去吧
There you go.
为什么诺兰在度蜜月的时候要跟我视频
Why is Nolan FaceTiming me from his honeymoon?
你打电话来是想用岛屿上的
Are you calling to rub in how beautiful
天堂生活酸我们吗
ydyr island paradise is?
是就好了
I wish.
这地方已经一塌糊涂了
Place is run down,
电话和网络都很不稳定
phone and internet are very spotty,
窗外还有个变态
there was a creeper outside our window
偷窥我们睡觉整整一个小时
watching us sleep for an hour,
我们刚刚又发现了一具尸体
and now we found a body.
尸体吗
A body?
是的
Yeah.
我们清洁工刚被冲到海滩上
The housekeeper just washed up on the beach.
这里有点不对劲
Something is wrong here,
当地执法机构几乎是形同虚设
and local law enforcement is non- existent.
我担心有人发现了我是警察
I'm worried somebody maybe found out I was a cop
然后针对我 你能
and is targeting- - could you- -
诺兰
Nolan.
看来他需要支援
Seems like he needs some backup.
你是建议来一次热带旅行吗
Are you suggesting a trip to the tropics?
本来不想的 现在想了
Iwasn't, but now Iam.
格雷警长 我们有麻烦了
Sergeant Grey, we have a problem.
诺兰刚打来电话
Uh, Nolan just called.
他们在沙滩上发现了一具尸体
They found a dead body on the beach.
为什么我已经感觉习以为常了
Why do I feel like I should be more surprised about that?
是啊 他和贝莉基本上属于柯南体质
Yeah, he and Bailey are basically trouble magnets.
他没带配枪
Hmm. He doesn't have his gun.
没有支援
No backup.
而现在他身处一个活跃的犯罪现场
And now he's in the middle of an active crime scene.
我们想去支援
We want to go down there.
去一个你们没有管辖权的小岛吗
To an island where you have no jurisdiction?
等到你们拿到差旅批准时
By the time you get the funds approved to book the travel,
他都要庆祝结婚纪念日了
he'll be celebrating his anniversary.
我可以先记在卫斯理的信用卡上
Ican put it on Wesley's card,
严格来说就是我的信用卡
which is also technically my card.
他总是说我们应该去度个假
He's always saying we should take a vacation.
那么部门就可以给我们报销了
And then the department can reimburse us.
你知道头等舱是不能报销的
You know they won't cover first class.
但是用信托基金可以报
But the trust fund does.
好吧 说真的
OK, seriously,
你们觉得诺兰需要被拯救吗
do you think Nolan needs saving,
还是你们想溜出办公室摸鱼
or are you just trying to get out the office?
鱼和熊掌就不能兼得嘛
Who says two things can't coexist?
塞琳娜 下班后我们能聊聊吗
Uh, Celina, can we talk after shift?
不是没事
It's not fine.
THO N 你说什么
Come again?
我今早说
I know I said this morning that the- -
那个吻没啥大不了的
that the kiss wasn't a big deal.
但其实心里还是觉得很别扭
But the truth is, I still feel weird.
我必须接受这一点
And I have to be OK with that.
你也得接受这一点
You need to be OK with that.
是的 当然
Yeah, of course.
怎么做
How?
我 我不知道
I- - I don't know.
我也希望咱俩能恢复正常
I want us to get back to normal too
但这需要时间 好吗
But it's- - it's going to take some time, OK?
在这段时间内 尴尬是难免的
And it will be weird until it isn't.
菜鸟
Boot!
你需要在你脖子上挂个铃铛吗
I'm about to hang a bell around your neck,
你总是一扭头就不见了
cause I keep losing you.
文书工作都做完了吗
You get that paperwork all done?
是的 长官
Oh, yes, sir.
我轮班结束前
Is there anything else you need
还需要我做什么吗
before I end my shift?
你觉得呢
What do you think?
我
I- -
CHEN 该做的都做完了
You are all done.
打卡下班吧 今天干得不错
Clock out Good work today.
谢谢 晚安
Thank you Good night.
晚安
Good night.
给她一点肯定你会死吗
Would it kill you to give her some acknowledgment?
我想帮她当个好警察
I'm trying to help her become a good cop,
而不是提升她的自尊
not boost her self- esteem.
对 但在培养新人时
Yeah, but when you're teaching someone,
肯定他们的进步
it's important to tell them what they're doing right
与指出他们的不足同样重要
as well as what they can improve upon.
是啊 这种方法用来
Yeah, it sounds like a good plan
培养平庸之辈确实不错
if you re going for mediocre.
你是一点都没被我软化到吗
Have I not softened you at all?
我竟然有点紧张 会不会很奇怪
Is it weird that I'm nervous?
不 这不叫奇怪
No, it's not weird.
这叫可怕
This is creepy.
你觉得这声音是在交配还是在猎杀
Does that sourd like mating or killing to you?
岛上停电了
Power is out.
幸运的是 步入式冰箱用的是备用发电机
Fortunately, walk- in fridge runs on a backup generator.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
一半儿的我准备好了
Part of me is
另一半儿只觉得纯纯悲伤
and a part of me just feels sad.
看到人被这样放在这儿 真让人心碎
I hate seeing someone kept like this.
我也一样
Same here.
告慰她的最好方式
Best thing we can do for her is trying to figure out
就是找出真相
what really happened.
是啊 说得对
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
这里有摄像头
Some cameras here.
好的 我是洛杉矶警局的约翰·诺兰
AlI right. I am John Nolan, LAPD.
我是贝莉·努恩 急救人员
This is Bailey Nune, EMT.
我们正在对玛莎·德尔加朵进行外部尸检
We're doing an external autopsy on Martha Delgado.
我们于昨天在水中发现了她
We found her in the water yesterday.
死亡时间估计在8小时前
Time of death was estimated eight hours prior.
她已被冷藏了6个小时
She's been in cold storage for six hours,
加在一起 一共是14个小\时了
giving us approximately 14 hours postmortem.
手指看上去无异常
Her fingers look good.
人在中毒后 指甲通常
Usually with some sort of poisoning,
会变色或出现白纹
there's a color change or white lines on the nails.
没有看到任何瘀伤
Not seeing any bruising.
等等
Hang on a sec.
她左耳后有一处撕裂伤
Got a- - it's a laceration behind her left ear.
她在落水时撞到头了吗
Did she hit her head when she fell in the water
还是先被击中才落水的
or was she hit and then fell in?
这只有正式尸检时才能判断
No way to tell without a proper autopsy.
我们来检查下她的口袋
Let's go through her pockets,
看看里面有没有东西
see if there's anything in there
能解答我们的疑惑
that might fill in the blanks.
约翰
John.
那是什么
What is that?
绷带钳
A bandage claw.
也许是她打扫迪安房间时
Maybe she picked it up
捡到的
when cleaning Dean's room.
然后不换衣服还带着它去游泳么
And then took it for a swim with all her clothes on?
你认为是他杀的她吗
Do you think he killed her?
我不知道
I don't know.
但我觉得有必要去他小屋看看
But I am starting to think we need to check out his cabin.
你的手呢
Where's your hand?
我就在这儿 这里好黑
I'm right here. It's so dark.
灯全都熄了
The lights are off.
对 而且还停电了
Yeah, and the power's out too.
就算灯开着也没用
So that's no help.
你觉得他会在里面么
You think he's in there?
只有一个办法能知道了
Only one way to find out.
好的
OK.
没人 我们走
Empty. Let's go.
好的
OK.
好
这家伙没带多少行李
This guy travels light.
-在那儿  -好的
There. - OK.
很好
Great.
等等
Oh, wait.
我找到些东西 你看
I found something. Here.
这是什么
What is this?
这可不是普通的狩猎装备
That is not your average hunting equipment.
好吧
OK, um
枪上没有序列号
there's no serial number.
-把弹药拆掉吧  -万一他注意到了呢
Let's take the ammo. What if he misses it?
总比他开枪强吧
Well, better than him using it.
等等
Wait, wait.
我把枪他的管卡住
I'm jamming the barrel.
来 这样应该行了
Here. That'll do it.
走吧
Let's go.
他来了
It's him.
后门
Back door.
快走 走走
Go, go, go.
-你在干什么  -设置相机
What are you doing? - The camera.
走吧
Come on!
快走 快走
Let's go, let's go!
刚才好险啊
That was close.
好吧
OK.
他还在那儿
He's still there.
也许他打算回房睡觉了
Maybe he's calling it a night?
或者是过来杀我们的
Or coming to try to murder us.
最近的岛也在三小时之外
The nearest island is at least three hours away.
我们划皮艇的话 能在日出前赶到
We could grab a kayak and be there by sunrise.
然后我们通知警察
So we notify police.
让他们赶到岛上
They head over here,
在迪安吃完早餐前 将他逮捕
arrest Dean before he finishes breakfast.
你觉得如何 在月光下划皮艇
What do you say? Kayaking by moonlight?
-比比谁先到  -是的
- I'|I race you there. - Yeah.
我们的逃跑计划没预想中顺利
So there's an issue with our escape plan.
我去 这得费不少力呢
I mean, this took work!
肯定是趁我们验尸时破坏的
Must have done that while we were examining the body.
他知道我们盯上他了
He knows we're onto him.
这次蜜月绝对终身难忘
This has certainly been a memorable honeymoon.
除了你 我不想和任何人一起度过
There's no one else I'd rather spend it with than you.
哦 亲爱的
Oh, sweetie.
要是哈珀或洛佩兹在你身边
I mean, except you may be better off
你可能会更开心
with Harper or Lopez.
或者是蒂姆和露西
Or Tim or Lucy.
对 还有格雷 塞琳娜
Right. Grey, Celina.
亚伦
Aaron.
天 连斯密提我都可以
Heck, I'd even accept Smitty
只要他带着枪过来
right now if he brought his gun.
这是伊丽丝 她看起来很害怕
That's Elise. She looks bad.
-我得过去  -不 等等等等
I'm gonna go. - No, wait, wait, wait, wait.
没关系 别担心
It's OK. It's OK.
-我马上就回来  -约翰 不要
I will be right back. - John, no!
-我马上回来  -不要
- I'|| be right back. - No.
天啊
Oh, my God.
不
No
约翰
John!
现在几点了
What time is it?
天啊 都这么晚了
Oh, my God, it's so late.
说明你缺觉
You needed to sleep.
不 我应该在复习才对
No, I should be studying.
请一个上午的假吧
Ah, take the morning off.
你不觉得好些了吗
Don't you feel better?
感觉确实不错
You know, I do.
谢谢你
Thank you.
天呐
Oh, my God.
我的考试还有20分钟开始
My test is in 20 minutes!
什么 怎么会
What? How?
他们把时间提前了
They moved it up!
我手机没信号 你呢
No service. You?
也没有
Nope
也就是说 我们无法追踪他他俩的手机
Which means we can't track their phones
也无法得知后援仆么时候到来
or get an ETA on our backup
这里感觉怪怪的
I don't like this.
是啊 一个跟你打招呼的人都没有
Yeah, there is no one around to greet you.
就算大喊大叫也没人听见
Or hear you scream.
那是动物的叫声吧
That that was just an animal, right?
是啊 但以防万一
Sure. But just in case.
好的
OK.
你好 我是露西·陈
Um, hi, I'm Lucy Chen,
我是来参加警探考试的
and I'm here for the detective's exam.
-陈  -对
Chen. Mm- hmm.
好的
Right.
先坐一下
Take a seat.
几个小时后就会排到你
They'll be with you in a few hours.
但是 但我收到短信说
Um- - no, um, but I got a text from them.
需要我马上过来
They said that they needed me right away.
我能说啥呢
What can I tell you?
等着吧
Over there.
排到你时会叫你的
They'll get to you when they get to you.
嘿 她怎么样了
Hey. How's she doing?
你问塞琳娜还是露西
Celina or Lucy?
都问问
Both.
塞琳娜有进步
Celina is making progress.
她今天又该跟我巡逻了
I think she's riding with me again today.
露西去考试了 正在等着叫号
Lucy's in the test now waiting her turn.
她早点考完 我也早点轻松
I'll be glad when this is done.
嘿 我调查了一下那个无名氏
Hey, I did some research on the security badge
衣服上的胸牌
our John Doe was wearing.
那家公司在洛杉矶有数十家企业客户
The company patrols dozens of businesses in LA.
他一直在说北韩 对吧
He kept talking about North Korea, right?
其中一个企业的办公楼
Well, one of the office buildings
就在南韩城 离我们发现他的地方
is in Koreatown, just a few blocks
只有几个街区
from where we found him.
他为啥要戴个假胸牌
Why the fake badge?
这家公司四楼有一个钻石交易所
The company has a diamond exchange on the fourth floor.
你觉得他是打算抢劫吗
And you think he was gonna rob it?
没错 应该是中途遇上意外
Exactly. I think something went wrong.
他受了伤 失了忆
He got injured and lost his memory.
也没更好的解释了
Not any better ideas.
我们先去看看吧
Let's go check it out.
千得好
Great work.
走吧 新人
Let's go, Boot.
安全
Clear.
他们在这装满了摄像头
They put up cameras all over the place.
All right. 好吧
最后一段录像肯定上传到什么地方了
The last footage has to be uploaded somewhere.
给它充个电 瞧瞧录下来什么了
Let's get this charged, see what we can find.
哪面墙后面是钻石交易所
AlI right, so which wall is the diamond exchange behind?
那一面
That one.
好的
OK.
他是想通过共用墙
So it looks like he tried to break
闯进钻石交易所
into the diamond exchange through a shared wall,
然后从天花板上摔下 把自己撞晕了
fell through the ceiling, knocked himself out instead.
外面有人在吗
Is someone there?
谁
Hello?
兄弟 把我弄出去
Hey, man, get me out of herel
警察里面有人吗
Police. Someone in there?
帮帮我 我被困住了
Help me. I'm stuck!
谢天谢地 你们找到我了
Thank God you found me.
我就知道罗杰不会丢下我的
I knew Roger wouldn't leave me behind.
我就知道
I knew it.
我只是希望你们能早来五分钟
I just wish you got here five minutes earlier...
我也就不用喝自己的尿了
before I drank my own urine.
陈警官
Officer Chen.
晚上好
Good evening.
谢谢你们
Thank you for- -
我们都面了一天了
It's been a long day,
就直接开始吧
so let's just get right to it.
如果一名记者想要进入犯罪现场
What would you do if a member of the press
你会怎么做
wanted access to a crime scene?
媒体比普通民众有更多权利
The press are allowed closer access to a crime scene
接近犯罪现场
than the general public.
当且仅当记者不会破坏证据
It is acceptable for the press to enter a crime scene
或危及自己安全时 就可以
if and only if they are not going to disturb the evidence
让记者进入犯罪现场
or endanger themselves.
我们来聊聊不破坏证据的
Let's talk about the importance
重要性
of not disturbing evidence.
你最近在一次办案中 没能保护好犯罪现场
Recently, you- - you failed to secure a crime scene.
-是的  -然后呢
- I did. And?
触发了洒水装置
The sprinklers went off.
关键证据被冲走了
Critical evidence was literally washed away.
我尽最大所能恢复了证据 并跟地方检察官合作
I recovered what I could, and I worked with the DA
让案子站住了脚
to make the case as strong as possible.
这是我的错
It was my fault.
我对那件事负全部责任
I accept full responsibility for that.
但我充分挽回了情况
But I made the most of it.
听上去 你把证据弄丢了 自己似乎还挺得意
It sounds like you're almost glad you lost evidence.
当然不是
Of course not.
但我无法改变事实
But I couldn't change it.
我没让这件事影响我的办案目标
And I didn't let it knock me off my course.
我追到了嫌犯 拿到了他的全部供词
I tracked my suspect, and I got a full confession.
那次错误给了我很大教训
I learned a lot from that mistake,
我再也不会犯了
and I will never make it again.
东边好像有几间小木屋
Looks like there's a few cabins in the east.
好的 播放吧
AlI right. Here we go.
看看你们做了什么
Look what you did.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧 我们得马上找到他们
All right We gotta find them now.
哪个方向是东
Which way is east?
嗯 那边
Uh, that way.
我们走
Let's go.
我来这是要寻找宁静
I came here for peace and quiet
我是来疗愈的
To heal.
你们搞砸了这一切
And you screwed that up.
我终于可以变帅了
I was finally gonna be good- looking.
像你这样的辣妹
And hot girls like you
终于要对我多看一眼了
were finally gonna look my way.
现在我会把她们都吓跑
And now they'll- - now they'll just run.
真正的美是内在的
True beauty is on the inside.
哦 好啊
Oh. [laughs]Good.
你介意我给你开个口子 看看你的内在吗
Then you won't mind me cutting my way inside you to find it?
嘿 别上手
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoal
听着 冲我来
Look, focus on me
你的一切都是我搞砸的
I'm the one who screwed everything up for you.
-是我干的  -别吃醋
It was me. Don't be jealous
咱们能玩的有很多呢
There's plenty of this to go around, huh?
你是警察 对吧
You're a cop, aren't you?
是的
Yes.
对 我是洛杉矶警察
Yes, I am, LAPD.
但我们来这儿和你无关
But us being here has nothing to do with you.
我们是在度蜜月
We're on our honeymoon.
是呢
Rightl
你们这个行动阵仗还挺大
It's a whole operation.
拉斐尔和伊丽丝本就在这工作
"It's a"- Rafael and Elise work here.
你以为他们是卧底吗
What, you- - you thought they were undercover?
-你对我知道多少  -一无所知
- What do you know about me? - Nothing.
如果你不来招惹我们
And we wouldn't have suspected anything
我们本来也不会起疑的
if you'd just left us alone!
你是个骗子
You are a liar!
闭嘴
Shut up!
不然就跟你爸一样 死定了
Or you're gonna end up as dead as your dad!
顺便说一句 拆掉子弹这一招很聪明
By the way, you were smart to take my ammo,
但你藏得不太好
but you didn't hide it very well.
枪声
Gun.
-你还好吗  -我没事
You OK? - Yeah, I'm OK.
快把我吓死了
I was so scared.
去浴室拿几条毛巾
Get some towels from the bathroom.
-我得给她止血  -好的
I need to stop her bleeding. - Right.
-来了  -好的 好的
I got it. Yeah, yeah.
你会没事的
It's gonna be OK.
这是什么 天啊
What is- oh, my God.
这肯定是你的
I believe that's yours.
这是谁来了
Who the hell is that?
我们的后援到了
That's our backup, finally.
看来我们的蜜月要以直升机结束了
Looks like our honeymoon ends with an airlift.
谢天谢地
Thank God.
你今天表现不错 菜鸟
You did good work today, Boot.
注重细节 思维新颖
Paid attention to details, thought outside the box.
谢谢你
Thank you.
多亏了教官的指导
I couldn't have done it without my training officer.
答得好
That's a good answer.
但今天还没结束
But day's not done yet.
是啊 没错
Right, right.
但你知道 如果有我教官帮忙
But you know, this could be a little more manageable
这项工作可能更好办
with the help from my TO.
别给你点阳光就灿烂
Don't mistake my compliment for kindness.
警察工作就没有好办的
Police work isn't supposed to be manageable.
-祝你好运  -是 长官
Good luck. - Yes, sir.
我听说有人吐在你身上了
I heard a guy vomited on you,
你还抓了一个喝了自己尿的家伙
and then you booked another guy who drank his own urine?
是的
Yeah.
你现在肯定挺怀念巡逻的日子吧
You know, I bet you're missing patrol right about now.
我应该还能撑几天再回去
I think I can handle a few more days
至少不用被陌生人吐一身
without being covered in a stranger's bodily fluids.
今天感觉没昨天那么奇怪了 对吧
Today feels less weird than yesterday, doesn't it?
是的
Yeah.
也许明天感觉会更正常
And maybe tomorrow will feel even less weird.
似乎有道理
That sounds about right.
很好 因为
Good, cause I-
我想你这个朋友了
I miss my friend.
我也是
Me too.
也许未来某天 这事会成为我们之间的笑料
Maybe we can laugh about this sometime soon- -
夕不行 但愿会很快
not, like, today, but soon.
晚安 塞琳娜
Good night, Celina.
晚安
Good night.
警长 我会哭死在这个名单上的
Sarge, I'm gonna die on this list.
很抱歉 陈
Sorry, Chen.
哟哟哟
Well, well, well. AUTOI
史上最短的假期
The shortest vacation ever.
你们查到那个坏人的身份了吗
You get an ID on Nolan and Bailey's bad guy?
没错 他的真名是尼古拉斯·科尔斯顿
Yep, his real name is Nicholas Colston.
自从警察在他公寓发现他女友的残骸后
He has been in the wind since they found
他就一直下落不明
pieces of his girlfriend all over his apartment.
他躲去了岛上
He was hiding out on the island
从整容手术中恢复
recovering from facial surgery,
当他发现隔壁有个度蜜月的警察后
and when he saw a cop honeymooning next door,
就变得疑神疑鬼
he got paranoid.
以为受害者在监视他
He thought his victims were conducting surveillance.
很高兴你们及时赶到
Glad you got there when you did.
当地警方说 我们可能得
Well, local law says that we might have to go
回岛上一趟去作证
back down to the island to testify.
是的 一周 最多两周
Yeah. Week- - maybe two, tops.
行啊
Yeah.
真有意思
That's funny.
真不敢相信我排第17名
I can't believe I came in 17th.
比得倒数第一还难受
It's almost worse than coming in last.
不过 你想啊
Hey, look.
倒数第一肯定没奖品拿
There is definitely no prize for coming in last.
但第17名会有啊
But I'm pretty sure there's a prize for coming in 17th.
我天啊
Oh, my God.
看来我要把职业目标定在
I guess I'll just have to set my sights
别的方向了 比如都会司
on a different future, like metro.
我开玩笑啦
I'm kidding.
我 我知道的
I- - I knew that.
-是呢  -就是
Yeah, right- Yeah.
你真以为我会以第一的身份进去吗
You really thought I was gonna come in first?
当然了
Of course I did.
我要躺下歇歇了
JI'm gonna lay my head down J
很抱歉让你失望了
I'm sorry for disappointing you.
♪放我走 让我走♪
♪Let me go, let me go♪
你不可能让我失望的
You could never disappoint me.
♪慢慢地又轻柔♪
♪Nice and easy and slow♪
♪我说让我走吧♪
♪I said let me go♪
这话真可爱的
This is cute.
-我说的不错  -是不错
- I did a good job. - Yeah, you did.
♪我心中的岛屿 没错♪
♪Island in my mind, yes♪
♪我总去那里傲游♪
♪I go there all the time♪
♪如果我有时间♪
♪And if I only had some time♪
♪我会在现实中找到这个岛♪
♪I'd find this island in real life♪
♪扬帆驶向我心中的小岛♪
♪Set sail for the island in my mind♪
-真正的蜜月快乐  -真正的蜜月快乐
Happy honeymoon for real. - Happy honeymoon for real.
♪只要我有时间♪
♪And if I only had some time♪
♪我会找到治愈我的磐石♪
♪You know I'm gonna find my healing rock♪